<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>r8teful</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on r8teful</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>My name</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>So much has happened</title>
      <link>/post/somuchhashappened/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/somuchhashappened/</guid>
      <description>Who am I again? Hi and welcome to my very inconsistent blogging life! Today I will again share with you my thoughts and what has been going on with my life, but trust me, this post is the best one yet! (probably not true). I have been on my own again and for some reason this sparks my inner productivity beast that just wants to keep working, this is one of the reasons I’m writing here again, also for another reason I will discuss later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I have been up to</title>
      <link>/post/whatihavebeenupto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/whatihavebeenupto/</guid>
      <description>The Last Year A lot of things have happened since I last wrote something on this blog more then a year ago now. I spent half of that year abroad in Utrecht, The Netherlands where I met lots of cool people and socialized a lot. I also spent time traveling to various places inside Europe, one of being Antwerp where I watched the CS:GO Major which was one of the most enjoyable events I have been to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Journey</title>
      <link>/post/anewjourney/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/anewjourney/</guid>
      <description>Hey! This is the start of my personal blogging journey. I have been interested in documenting my personal development ever since I realized I couldn&amp;rsquo;t just play video games all day without any effort (which was about 3 years ago when I turned 18). Ever since then I&amp;rsquo;ve made different notes on different note taking apps and documents scattered all over the place. But I have not really had a specific spot for these things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Rik Muijs, otherwise known as r8teful, I was born in The Netherlands on August 1999 and moved to Sweden at age 6. My interests are in game development and content creation. I&amp;rsquo;m currently studying at Chalmers University for my Computer Science degree with a master in Interaction Design and Technologies with specialization in Game development. I love creating games and videos for people enjoy!
Background I have been into computers as far back as I can remember.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/games/temp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games/temp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
